Plus, I've been kind of talking
some smack about you.
(Bernadette:)-Hello, Howard.
-Wait, Bernadette, I need to talk to you.
-I can't. I'm working.
-This will only take a second.
(Howard:)You asked me to think about
where our relationship was going...
(Howard:)...and I did.
(Penny:)Bernadette...
(Howard:)...will you marry me?
(Bernadette:)Is this more comedy
that I don't understand?
(Howard:)No, I'm serious.
I'm never gonna find another girl
like you...
(Howard:)...who likes me and is, you know, real.
(Bernadette:)-So this isn't a joke?
-No.
(Bernadette:)Then you're insane.
(Howard:)I prefer to think of myself as quirky.
(Bernadette:)Howard, we've only been on three dates.
We haven't even had sex yet.
(Howard:)Fair enough. When's your break?
(Bernadette:)Wow.